Guide to the New York State College of Human Ecology Alumni Association records, [ca. 1928-2010].
New York State College of Human Ecology Alumni Association records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
New York State College of Human Ecology Alumni Association records, [ca. 1928-2010].
23-11-2813
New York State College of Human Ecology.Alumni Association.
3.6 cubic ft.
Correspondence, minutes, reports, financial records, and other records of the Association.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, minutes, reports, financial records, and other records of the Association.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York State College of Human Ecology.; Cornell University--Alumni and alumnae.
Subjects:
Human ecology--Study and teaching.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- June 1928-June 1950 (Box 1, Folder 1A)
  - Attendance at annual meeting, June 15, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 1A)
  - Attendance at annual meeting, June 16, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 1A)
  - Minutes, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 1A)
  - List of Members, 1940-1941 (Box 1, Folder 1A)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 1A)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 1A)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 1A)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 1A)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 1A)
  - Memo to seniors (Box 1, Folder 1A)
- June 1950-June 1955 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, June 1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Remarks by Dean Vincent, June 9, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - President's Report, 1951-1953 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, June 1951 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Members of the Exec. Comm., 1953-1955 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, June 12, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes of Exec. Comm., November 19, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes of Exec. Comm., April 6, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Treasurer's Report, June 11, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, June 11, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, August 5, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, October 18, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Report of Exec. Comm., November 2, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, April 12, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1954-55 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Explanation of changes of bylaws (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Constitution and bylaws, May 11, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- June 1955-June 1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, June 10, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, August 5, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, November 29, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee, April 9, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Letter to alumni, May 15, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, June 8, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, July 20, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Secretary's Report, June 1957 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, June 7, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, July 23, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Minutes of Executive Committee, November 21, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Secretary's report, April 3, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Letter to graduates, May 24, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Treasurer's report, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, June 13, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee, October 6, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee, February 24, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee, April 21, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Notes from Dean Canoyer (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bio. sketches of executive committee candidates, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, June 12, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee, September 28, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Various Committee Records, 1961-1970 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee, January 16, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee, March 24, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee, April 9, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Letter to alumni, May 26, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Treasurer's Report, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cost of Bulletins, newsletters, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- June 1960-May 1962 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Minutes & Treasurer’s reports (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Annual meeting, June 19, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Executive Committee, September 19, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Executive Committee, January 7, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Executive Committee, April 8, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Chart - cost of alumni newsletter (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence from D. Canoyer to HEAA pres., May 10, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Committee Chairman (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Minutes & Treasurer's reports (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Annual Meeting, June 9, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Schedule of events (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Executive Committee, September 23, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Executive Committee, January 6, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Executive Committee, March 31, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Chart - cost of alumni newsletter (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence re: structure of HEAA, July 5, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- June 1962-May 1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Committee Chairman (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Annual Report (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Secretary's Report (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Minutes & Treasurer's reports
    - Annual Meeting, June 8, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Executive Committee, September 22, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Executive Committee, November 17, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Executive Committee, January 19, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Executive Committee, March 16, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- June 1963-May 1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Committee Chairman (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Minutes & Treasurer's reports (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Annual Meeting, June 14, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Executive Committee, September 19, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Executive Committee, November 14, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Executive Committee, January 22, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Executive Committee, March 19, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Tentative budget, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Committee reports in minutes (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Special for Early Birds Institute for Community Leaders, April 30, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Chart - cost of HEAA newsletter, April 1963- March 1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Chart - cost of HEAA newsletter, April 1964-March 1965 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence
    - re: alumni newsletter history and purpose, February 11, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - re: alumni newsletter current format, February 13, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- June 1964-May 1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Committee Chairman (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Minutes & Treasurer's reports (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Annual Meeting, June 18, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Executive Committee, June 18, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Executive Committee, November 14, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Executive Committee, September 29, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Executive Committee, December 10, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Executive Committee, February 9, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Executive Committee, April 6, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Tentative budget, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Letters concerning College undertaking costs of both printed issues of the college newsletter, December 18, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Letters concerning College undertaking costs of both printed issues of the college newsletter, January 6, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - re: historical reference to HEAA, May 28, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- June 1965-May 1966 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Committee Chairman (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Minutes & Treasurer's reports (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Annual Meeting, June 18, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Executive Committee, June 18, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Executive Committee, September 20, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Executive Committee, November 9, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Institute for Community Leaders April 20-21, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Report of Scholarship Chairman (Box 1, Folder 7)
- June 1964-May 1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Committee Chairman (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Minutes & Treasurer's reports (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Annual Meeting, June 17, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Executive Committee, June 17, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Executive Committee, September 20, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Executive Committee, December 13, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Executive Committee, January 12, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Executive Committee, March 2, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Tentative budget 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Institute for Community Leaders, April 18, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Biographical sketches of Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 8)
- June 1967-May 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Committee Chairman (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Minutes & Treasurer's reports (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Annual Meeting, June 16, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Executive Committee, June 16, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Executive Committee, September 21, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Executive Committee, November 30, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Executive Committee, January 10, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Executive Committee, March 6, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Proposed budget 1967-68 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Contingent report 8 month statement (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Letter to President Perkins, November 30, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Wing dedication, May 13, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Institute for Community Leaders, May 14, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Dean's Breakfast, June 7, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- June 1968-May 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Committee Chairman (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Minutes & Treasurer's reports (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Annual Meeting, June 7, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Executive Committee, June 7, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Executive Committee, September 26, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Executive Committee, November 18, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Executive Committee, January 9, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Executive Committee, February 26, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Board of Directors, June 7, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Board of Directors, November 1, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Proposed budget, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Institute for Community Leaders, April 28-29, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Biographical sketches of Executive committee candidates (Box 1, Folder 10)
- June 1969-May 1970 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Committee Chairman (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Annual Report (President’s Message) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Minutes
    - Annual Meeting, June 13, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Executive Committee, June 13, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Executive Committee, September 25, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Executive Committee, November 20, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Executive Committee, January 29, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Proposed budget 1969-1970
  - Final Treasurer's Report, June 10, 1969- June 9, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Name Change of Alumni Association (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - President's Message (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Dues Mailing (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Profile - Lucy Jarvis (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Dean Knapp conference outline, September 16, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- June 1970-May 1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Committee Chairman (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Minutes & Treasurer's Reports
    - Annual Meeting, June 12, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Executive Committee, June 12, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Executive Committee, September 18, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Executive Committee, November 20, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Executive Committee, January 29, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Executive Committee, April 30, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Proposed budget, 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- June 1971-May 1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Committee Chairman (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Minutes
    - Annual Meeting, June 11, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Executive Committee, June 11, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Executive Committee, September 17, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Executive Committee, November 19, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Executive Committee, January 21, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Executive Committee, April 14, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Annual Financial Report, June 10, 1971 - June 9, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Report of 1972 Legislative Forum (Box 1, Folder 13)
- June 1972-May 1973 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Committee Chairman (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Minutes
    - Annual Meeting, June 9, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Executive Committee, June 9, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Executive Committee, September 29, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Executive Committee, November 17, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Executive Committee, February 2, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Proposed Budget, 1972-73 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Quarterly Financial Statement (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Letter to Alumni, September 1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- June 1973-May 1974 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Committee Chairman (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Annual Report (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Minutes
    - Annual Meeting, June 8, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Executive Committee, June 8, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Executive Committee, October 5, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Executive Committee, November 9, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Executive Committee, February 1, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Executive Committee, April 5, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Annual Financial Report, June 8, 1973 - June 13, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Proposed Budget, 1973-74 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Quarterly Financial Reports, June 8, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Report of Contributions, 1972-73 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- June 1974-May 1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Committee Chairs (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Annual Report (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Minutes
    - Annual Meeting, June 14, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Executive Committee, June 14, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Executive Committee, September 27, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Executive Committee, November 15, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Executive Committee, January 31, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Executive Committee, March 7, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Executive Committee, April 11, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Annual Financial Report, June 8, 1973 - June 13, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Proposed Budget, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Quarterly Financial Reports (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Scholarship committee report, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Statistics on membership, January 1970- January 1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Letter to Alumni, September 9, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Letter to Alumni, April 7, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Alumni information & remarks (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Alumni Association elections ballot (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - NY Times article, December 13, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- June 1975-May 1976 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Committee Chairman (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Directors-at-Large (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Minutes
    - Annual Meeting, June 13, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Executive Committee, June 13, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Executive Committee, March 26, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Alumni Board, September 26, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Alumni Board, November 7, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Alumni Board, January 30, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Treasurer's reports
    - Annual Financial Report, June 13, 1974 - June 1, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Proposed Budget & notes, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Report, November 7, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Alumni Scholarships and Grants, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Alumni breakfast program, June 13, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Membership Letter to Alumni, September 8, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Open house program, 15, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Letter to Board, November 17, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Various Committee Records, 1976-1978 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- June 1976-May 1977 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Committee Chairman (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Directors-at-Large (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Annual Report (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Minutes
    - Annual Meeting, June 11, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Alumni Board Meeting, June 11, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Alumni Board Meeting, September 17, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Alumni Board Meeting, Novermber 19, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Alumni Board Meeting, Janurary 28, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Alumni Board Meeting, March 11, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Presentation notes Cornell Club NYC, November 5, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Treasurer's reports (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Proposed Budget, 1976-77 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - HE Alumni Scholarships and Grants (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - HE news contents, May 1977 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Ballot (for 1976-78 term) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Summary of 1976 open house (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Tentative open house program, November 12, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Letter to Alumni, September 1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- June 1977-May 1978 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Committee Chairman (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Directors-at-Large (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Minutes
    - Annual Meeting, June 10, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Executive Committee, June 10, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Alumni Association, September 23, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Alumni Association, December 2, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Alumni Association, March 10, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Treasurer's report, 1977-78 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Display Case Committee, June 1977 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Jean Failing Fellowship Fund, October 1977 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - HE Alumni scholarships & grants, 1977-78 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Cost of November HE News (Box 1, Folder 19)
- June 1978-May 1979 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Committee Chairman (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Directors-at-Large (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Annual Report (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Minutes
    - Annual Meeting, June 9, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Board of Directors, June 9, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Board of Directors, November 17, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Various Committee Records, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Board of Directors, January 19, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Executive Board, September 22, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Executive Board, November 17, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Executive Board, March 16, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Treasurer's reports
    - Actual budget, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Budget, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Budget, September 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Budget, November 17, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Proposed budget, January 19, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Treasurer's report, March 16, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Treasurer's report, June 8, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Alumni & Development report, August 4, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Scholarship report, September 25, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Scholarship report, February 20, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Membership report, March 14, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Constitution report, June 12, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - HE student financial aid funds, April 1979 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Letter, August 8, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Loans & grants policy, November 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- June 1979-May 1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Board of Directors (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Officers (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Committee Chairs & members (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Annual Report (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Minutes
    - Annual Meeting, June 8, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Board Meeting, June 8, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Executive Board Meeting, September 14, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Executive Board Meeting, November 8, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Various Committee Records, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Executive Board Meeting, January 18, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Executive Board Meeting, March 28, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Executive Board Meeting, June 8, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Treasurer's reports
    - Treasurer's report, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Budget, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Budget, June 8, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Budget, September 14, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Budget, November 8, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Budget, March 28, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Budget, June 13, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Committee reports (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - HEAA Scholarship & grant receipts, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Graduate recipients, September 12, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Charter life members, September 13, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Draft of letter to Admissions Policy Committee, April 15, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Memo for record, April 23, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Transfer Day program, March 28, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Funding required for HE newspaper (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Committee listing & definitions (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Rationale submitted by Constitution Revision Committee
- June 1980-May 1981 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Board of Directors (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Committee Chairs (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Annual Report (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Minutes
    - Annual Meeting, June 13, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Board Meeting, June 13, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Board Meeting, October 4, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Various Committee Records, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Board Meeting, January 23, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Board Meeting, March 6-7, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Treasurer's report, January 1, 1980 - December 31, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Proposed budget, January 1, 1981 - December 31, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Investment proposal (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - March 6-7 program (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Discussion groups (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Nominations (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Alumni Contributions to admission (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Life membership (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Alumni Ambassadors, January 5, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 14th Confederation Annual Conference (Box 1, Folder 22)
- June 1981-May 1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Board of Directors (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Committee Chairs (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Annual Report (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Minutes
    - Annual Meeting, June 12, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Executive Committee, June 12, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Board of Directors, June 12, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Board of Directors, September 19, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Various Committee Records, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Board of Directors, January 22, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Board of Directors, January 23, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Board of Directors, April 30, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Treasurer's report, January 1 - December 1, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Budget, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Treasurer's Report, January 1, 1982 - June 7, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Committee Reports
    - Display Case Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Special Events, September 1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Honors & Recognition, September 7, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Continuing Education, September 11, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 23)